Kunal Kumar

Enthusiastic Software Developer with a flair for creating elegant solution in the least amount of time having an experience of one year wherein I've built solutions for technical firms. I aim work to establish my self as a BRAND in this technical industry

k1509kunal@gmail.com

8709198459

in linkedin.com/in/kunal-kumar-59b672193

github.com/kunal042

EDUCATION

B.Tech Electronics and Communication

Arya College of Engineering & It, Jaipur

06/2018 - 06/2022

Senior Seconday Examination

B.N Ucch Vidayalaya, sehan, Vashali

05/2018

PROJECT

E-TOLL PLAZA

- This app of my team project in hacthon, organised by here techonolgy
- This app lets user select his journery and then pay the toll tax using razzorpay

E-COMMERCE WEBSITE

- This is a project with the objective to develop a website where a consumer is provided with a shopping application
- Tech is used in the application for frontend HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstarp5, and for backend Dajngo

Blog Page

- This project is make to write blog when you login in the website ,Tech is used Django
- In this application make dyanmic Url, Authentication, login, logout, Dashboard of the blog were post, edit, delete operation

EXPERIENCE

INNOVATION ENGINEER

Stemrobo Technologies Pvt. ltd.

06/2023 - Present Website Development/Machine Learning

Develope company website and LMS System

- Task: To Authencation, Login, logout, credential of LMS, admin panel
- Develope when person show number of finger in front of camera led will glow to match of finger, also add to make facial Expression like when you are sad led glow red, simle led green etc and also work on microbit
- Also Trained Teachers/Students about Arduino, Robotics and AI

INTERSHIP

Ducat

08/2022 - 05/2023

AchiePyhton FullStack Developmentvements/Tasks

- Learn Pyhton make bank application using Simple Pyhton
- Learn HTML,CSS, make landing page, contact, about, login signup page,
- Learn Javascript: make smart calculator and add some effect on the website,
- Learn Django : clone E-Commerce website
- Learn React: Make a news web application using news API, also learn Redux

SKILLS



ACHIEVEMENTS

Secure 10th postions in Here Technology hacathon among 300+ Participate

Selection for Grand finals in SIH 2020

Secure 15th Position in RTU Hackathon among 300+ Participations conducted by Shankara Institute Of Technology, jaipur

I have organised Zypher tech Fest in my college

SPORTS PROGRAMMING

Hacker Rank (4*Star)

Geeks of Geeks

CERTIFICATES

Auto - Cad

SBPDCL

BSNL

Noida

LANGUAGES

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

English

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

